Wealth. Fame. Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Until someone proves it real.
Through it all?
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are.
On the cruise.
Don't call it murder, Jango.
I don't like the sound of it.
Oh, right, accident.
It's an accident that you planned.
Uh, what are those guys talking about?
Just be quiet.
Maybe if we listen a little
closer, we can find out?
We can't simply kill her.
It is critical to our plan that Miss
Kaya perishes in an unfortunate accident!
So don't screw that up.
So basically, on your signal,
the men and I stormed
the village and managed
to accidentally kill the little rich girl.
Then you get her inheritance
and we all get paid, right?
You moron!
Your ignorance is astounding.
We're not related, so how could
I inherit anything from her?
You'll work very hard to.
No, Jango, I won't.
Now listen to me.
This is the most important part.
Before you kill her, you'll use your
hypnosis to make Kaya write her will.
and it will say I leave my entire
fortune to my butler, Klahadore.
Then and only then will I
have undisputed control of
her enormous fortune and no
one will suspect a thing.
I have spent three long years gaining
the trust of everyone around me so that
it would be unsurprising for her to leave
the entirety of her inheritance to me.
Three years as a butler for this, huh?
Huh?
You sure had us scared
back then, Captain Kuro.
Three years ago, you suddenly said
you were giving up life as a pirate.
In no time at all, you set
up someone to be your double.
Then you let the world see
Captain Kuro get executed.
Only now do I understand that was
just the beginning of this plan.
You are the man of a thousand plans!
Never call me that again.
I abandoned that name years ago.
I now wish to obtain my wealth without
attracting the attention of the government.
In other words, I'm a pacifist.
The pacifist you are.
Murdering an entire family doesn't
exactly qualify as peaceful.
Hold on, I haven't
murdered an entire family.
The father's death wasn't planned.
Whatever you say, it
makes no difference to me.
If it's all the same to you,
hurry up and give the word.
The crew is getting bored.
We've been waiting in the waters
near here for over a week.
And the men are growing
more anxious by the minute.
This is horrible.
This is really horrible!
What are they talking about?
Is it bad guy stuff?
What weren't you listening to any of that?
Those guys aren't just bad.
They're evil.
Captain Kaido is known to be the
most devious skimming pirate around.
And though he's known for his smarts,
he's legendary for his brutality.
Word had it that the Marines caught
and executed him three years ago.
But Captain Kuro is alive and
well, posing as Clawdor the butler.
And he's had his diabolical sights set on
Kaya's fortune for the last three years.
First they'll attack the
village, then they'll kill Kaya!
This is bad!
This is seriously bad!
Hey, get down! I'll see you!
Hey, bad guys!
You better stay away from that girl!
Who are you?
You idiot! They spotted you!
Come on, hurry up and hide before they
decide you need a long, slow death!
Well now, if it isn't Usopp,
the mischievous town liar...
Oh, no!
I'm spotted too!
Did you...
hear anything?
Uh, no. Nothing at all.
I don't know what you mean.
We didn't hear a peep.
We just got here.
so we didn't hear anything about anything.
We heard it all.
Shut up!
Well, if you say so.
Pay attention, boys.
And watch this ring closely.
Okay.
Don't you get it?
It's some kind of weapon.
We gotta run.
By the count of Jango, you
will be in a deep sleep.
Are you ready?
One, run for cover.
He's going to kill us!
Jungle!
Jungle, you idiot!
I see you're still
falling asleep on the job.
Hey, be careful.
You're going to fall.
He had to go and fall
off a cliff, didn't he?
A pity, really.
I didn't mean to kill him.
But there's no way he could have survived.
This can't be happening.
They killed him?
He's really dead
What about the other one?
Shall I take care of him?
There's no need.
Everything he could say
would sound like lies!
Django, tomorrow at daybreak.
The men are to attack the village.
Rough up the villagers some.
And tear up their homes a
little for good measure.
And above all.
Make sure Miss Kaya's
death looks accidental?
Tomorrow?
Just accept it, Usopp.
There is nothing you can say or do to warn
the villagers of this impending tragedy.
Are you sure about that one?
Of course I am.
My plans are flawless.
I can't believe this!
This is terrible!
I gotta do something!
Everyone in the village I grew up with is
in danger, and Kaeya's going to be killed!
Who are you?
I'm Usopp, brave warrior of the sea.
I heard you've been a little down lately,
so I thought I'd tell you
a story to cheer you up.
You would do well to
mind your own business.
Please leave, or I'll call
someone who will make you leave.
And Ben?
What happened after that?
I fought, of course.
No!
Captain!
Hold on.
I thought Luffy was
supposed to be with him.
Captain!
Hey, where's Luffy?
Is he still at the shore?
Wow he looks really upset
but why still mad at the
butler who knows no that
wasn't just a mad face?
That look was different he was a
tragic face of sheer desperation.
Hey why don't you guys show us
the way to get down to that shore?
This smells like an adventure to me.
Yeah something happened at Sure, I
think this calls for the use of pirates!
Enough already!
How do we get to this place?
Terrible news!
Pirates!
Pirates are coming! Everybody run!
We don't stand a chance!
Everybody run! Run!
Tomorrow morning they're
gonna attack the village!
We gotta get out of here!
What are you doing? Run!
All right, Usopp.
Enough is enough.
We can't take it anymore.
We're putting a stop to this here and now.
It's for your own good.
No, it's not like that.
It's the truth this time.
I promise. Stop it.
We all know that you're
nothing but a liar.
It would do you some good to follow
Clawdor's example of hard work and honesty.
Everything he could say
would sound like lies.
Oh, no!
This is exactly what
Clawdor is counting on!
He ignored me because he
knew no one would believe me!
Are these to your liking, miss?
Custom-made to your exact specifications
It was quite a trip to get
them They're just perfect
Thank you so much for traveling
so far to get them for me
They're a gift, aren't they? Yes,
as of tomorrow it will be exactly three
years to the day since
Klahadore arrived here.
He's always taken such good care of me.
He'll be delighted to
receive such a lovely gift.
I hope so.
Please hear me out everyone!
Our lives depend on it!
Listen, pirates are going to
attack the village in the morning.
If we believed every story
you ever told us We would have
run screaming from the village
hundreds of times already.
Please believe me, we don't have time!
I'm not lying this time, I swear.
Don't you get it?
They'll murder you all You'll
be lucky if we don't murder you.
I'm not lying!
Get him!
Don't let him escape!
After three long years of absence, I
made the call for my men and you came.
Your loyalty will be richly rewarded.
I intend on being more than
generous when I divide the take.
At dawn tomorrow, destroy the village to
your heart's content. Oh, no! Kill him!
Kill him!
What?
Pirates are going to attack the village?
Then they're going to kill Kaya?
Yep, that's what they said.
No question about it.
So what made you think
it'd be a good time for
a nap that's the thing i
don't remember going to
sleep or getting down
here at all this proves
that clawador is a bad guy
Usopp saw right through
him I bet he's on his way
to warn the villagers so
they'll have time to run
away well that's perfect
Those stupid pirates
won't hurt anyone because
the town will be abandoned
by the time they get
Yeah, that's right.
We'd better run away,
too, if we want to live.
All right, let's pack our
treasure and run like the wind!
Oh, no! What's up?
We need to stock up before
the meat shop guy leaves!
Come on, that's not really
the issue at hand here.
Usopp?
Oh, good.
I was worried you wouldn't come back.
Quick, run, Kaeya!
They're gonna kill you!
Huh?
Someone's going to kill me?
He's tricked the entire village!
Clador's really a deadly pirate captain!
Is this a story?
Well, I don't like this one.
This isn't one of my
stories, it's the truth!
I heard it with my own ears.
Clawdor is a pirate captain who weaseled
his way into your family's home.
So he could steal your fortune.
He's pretended to be your
butler for three years.
So he could kill you
and inherit your money?
What are you talking about, Usopp?
His crew is going to
raid the village at dawn.
And in the process, you're
going to get killed!
Clawdor's a very bad man!
Your life is in danger!
You have to escape!
He did treat you harshly earlier,
and I understand that you're hurt.
But lying like this, it's not like you!
Kaya, please!
I'm telling you the truth!
I loved them. Every one. One.
All those lies you told me,
they brought joy to my heart.
But this is just vengeful poison.
Kaya, please, listen to me.
I'm not just trying to
get back at Klahadore.
Why would you do that? It's wrong.
Kaya, I...
Miss Kaya, is everything okay up here?
Let's get out of here!
Right now!
Unhand her immediately, you villain!
Please trust me, Kaia.
You gotta get out of this village
before that butler gets back!
Stop it!
Come on!
I promise this will all make sense
tomorrow, but right now we need to go!
Kaya, please, please trust me!
You're pathetic!
Leave Ms.
Kai alone, you maniac!
No!
Don't let that lunatic get away!
He broke in and tried to
kidnap the lady of the house.
Why why won't anyone believe me?
There, there, ma 'am.
Everything's going to be fine.
Captain!
Hey, how's it going, guys?
Hey, Captain! What is that?
Wait, you're alive again?
Alive?
Yeah, and I had a pretty good nap.
He was sleeping the whole time.
Captain, we heard all about those
pirates and their evil plan.
We better hurry and warn the people in
the village so they have time to get away.
Warn the people?
You're pathetic.
Stop it!
We all know you're nothing but a liar.
Ah!
Well, obviously I'm lying like usual.
That butler made me so
mad with what he said.
I thought I'd get him back
and say that he was a pirate.
Oh, I get it.
You put the Straw Hat guy up to it, too.
Hey, where are you going?
Honestly, you've really
disappointed me. Yeah.
Even though that butler guy is a jerk,
I thought you were better
than lying to hurt someone
and I admired you for being
such a kind-hearted person.
And I think we respected
you this entire time.
Let's go home.
Yeah, it's supper time anyways.
So, how come you lied to them?
Because all I do is lie.
There's no way anybody was
gonna believe what I had to say.
Why should they?
Because what you were telling
them was the honest truth.
They are coming, and they're
going to level this whole town.
Yeah, but what am I supposed to do?
They'll think I'm lying
if I try to warn them.
Everyone in the village thinks that tomorrow's
just going to be another normal day.
They think I'm lying, and
that's all they need to think.
I'm going to stop those pirates
at the beach tomorrow myself.
This is all my fault
for being such a liar.
I don't care anymore if they drive me
away with brooms or shoot me in the arm.
This is my village.
It's my home.
And I love everyone in it.
I have to protect them.
You're a hell of a good guy.
Sending your cronies away
and going into battle alone.
Just so you know.
I have dibs on all the
pirate treasure, you got it?
So you want a little help or what?
You guys, you're gonna help
me fight all these pirates?
I don't get it.
Well, you said there's a whole
bunch of bad guys, right?
And you look scared out of your mind.
For your information,
I have nerves of steel.
I'm perfectly okay with tons of bad guys.
After all, you're looking at
the legendary Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the high seas.
Damn it.
All right, fine, I'm scared.
Why shouldn't I be?
They're Captain Curl's men.
These guys mean business.
I don't need pity if you
guys are sticking around cuz
you pity me just leave I
don't need you laughing at me.
We're not laughing at you.
We're helping because you are honorable
You really think we risk
our lives out of pity?
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure.
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But the world ever changes.
I call out your name.
We could return to the time
when everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?